what computer should you get this is it
don't get anything more than this for
your first computer you really don't
need it if you're trying to get a
computer to learn not to play games not
to make videos not to do streaming
content if you're trying to learn Linux
this is the best computer I've used this
thing for 10 years I bought hundreds of
these for different students and they've
all come out amazingly the really great
thing is it's so cheap that anybody
messing it up doesn't have to be afraid
you buy it you don't spend over 300 $
you can go to Target and get it you
don't have to get it through Amazon The
Point here is you have a minimal
computer that on which to install Linux
or BSD or whatever you want and then you
can experiment I actually had one uh
student that I mentored install six
different Linux distributions by the
time I met with him again the week
following he actually ended up going
with Susie as his main Linux
distribution the point here is you want
to free yourself from the fear of
destroying the family computer or the
main computer that you have for school
or something like that so save up your
money instead of buying some overpriced
Educational Opportunity platform thing
you know pay 300 bucks and get yourself
a laptop put Linux on there and start
messing around with it